<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hero Path</string>
    <string name="choose_your_hero">Choose your hero!</string>
    <string name="hero_name_hint">Enter your hero name</string>
    <string name="start_adventure">Start the adventure</string>

    <string name="choose_next_step">Choose what to do, Mighty Hero!</string>
    <string name="go_to_town">Walk the city streets</string>
    <string name="go_to_dungeon">Go to creepy dungeon</string>
    <string name="go_to_tavern">Visit tavern</string>
    <string name="save_princess">Save the princess</string>
    <string name="retire">I should retire</string>
    <string name="clothes_in_blood">Your clothes are in blood after battle.</string>
    <string name="have_treasures">You\'re rich hero cause of treasures.</string>
    <string name="hero_drunk">You\'re drunk as hell.</string>
    <string name="hero_princess">Princess is by your side.</string>

    <string name="princess_dead_for_button">Princess is dead</string>
    <string name="princess_is_yours_button">Princess is already yours</string>
    <string name="princess_refused_you_button">Princess refused you</string>
    <string name="treasure_is_yours_button">You already have treasure</string>
    <string name="princess_forbid">Princess forbids you</string>

    <string name="retirement_descreption">You decided to end your hero days and retire. Here is what awaits you.</string>


    <string name="street_descr">You are walking down the central street of Ulugal, capital city of the Aurilia Kingdom.
    Building on both sides of the street are literal architectural wonders. People seem small in comparison, but some women
        looks even more marvelous than millennium old structures. Do you want to walk a little more?
    </string>
    <string name="button_continue">Walk a bit more</string>
    <string name="button_return">Return</string>

    <string name="dungeon_description">Dungeon is truly creepy. You hear moans of terrible creatures up ahead. But you are a Hero, and treasures await.</string>
    <string name="no_corridor">No path in this direction.</string>
    <string name="button_forward">Forward!</string>
    <string name="button_back">Back</string>
    <string name="button_left">Go left</string>
    <string name="button_right">Go right</string>
    <string name="dwarf_monsters">Monsters pity you and leave alive.</string>
    <string name="dwarf_traps">You are too short for spikes to reach you.</string>
    <string name="death">You die!</string>
    <string name="start_again">Start again?</string>

    <string name="tavern_description">It\'s a drinking contest. Push button to drink!</string>
    <string name="tavern_timer">30</string>
    <string name="tavern_drink">Drink!</string>
    <string name="tavern_try_again">Try again</string>

    <string name="tavern_class_dependencies_mage">You\'ve never drunk a pint in your life. What were you thinking?
    There is a spell that can save a man from intoxication, but you\'re too drunk to remember it. You are dead.</string>
    <string name="tavern_loose">You are not fast enough. You loose!</string>
    <string name="tavern_race_dependencies_elf">Elves have many natural talents but resistance to human alcohol is not one of them. You lose.</string>
    <string name="tavern_race_dependencies_dwarf">You\'re dwarf natural in drinking. You still sober enough to see how your opponent falls under the table. You win!</string>
    <string name="tavern_win">You win, the audience applaud you. Today you are proud of yourself. Let\'s not think of tomorrow morning.</string>
    <string name="princess_description">The time has come to save the princess. You enter the tower of evil magister.</string>

    <string-array name="choose_race">
        <item>Human</item>
        <item>Elf</item>
        <item>Dwarf</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choose_class">
        <item>Warrior</item>
        <item>Wizard</item>
        <item>Thief</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="race_description">
        <item>You\'re simple human, the most common race of Aurilon.</item>
        <item>You\'re Elf, beautiful, wise and cunning.</item>
        <item>You\'re dwarf, short but sturdy. Your homeland is deep underground.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="class_description">
        <item>People know you as noble warrior, protector of common folks.</item>
        <item>People know you as stubborn wizard, your only friends are dusty books. Sorry.</item>
        <item>People know you as cunning thief, that is the most profitable profession of Aurilon.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="street_variants">
        <item>You see sophisticated human lady dressed in a long dress with a low neckline.
        You fall in love and try to talk with her.</item>
        <item>You see the Palace of Yawning Prince. Paralyzed by its beauty you did not see
            a sneaky thief. 0 coins in your possession.</item>
        <item>Street gang ahead. The fight seems unavoidable.</item>
        <item>You are a bit tired but the garden ahead is so beautifull, so you walk a bit more.</item>
        <item>The hero is completely tired and want to pee.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="race_dependencies_lady">
        <item> She kisses you and say goodbye. You will never see her again. </item>
        <item>\"Sorry. Elves are too wild for my taste\".</item>
        <item>\"Meh. Go talk with some ugly dwarf woman, you midget.\"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="class_dependencies_gang">
        <item>But they are no match for your sword of legends. You leave behind cold bodies,
        severed heads and limbs, blood is all over you.</item>
        <item>But your best friend is fireball. One cast - seven burned bodies, and your clothes are clean.</item>
        <item>But you sneak past them with ease.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dungeon_rooms">
        <item>It is starting area.</item>
        <item>The room is full of monsters!</item>
        <item>Suspiciously quiet room.</item>
        <item>It\'s a trap! Awful spikes strikes at you from all sides.</item>
        <item>There is big four-headed albino dog in this room. It stares at you in hunger.</item>
        <item>Massive room with corridors at all sides.</item>
        <item>Lustful succubus waiting to kiss you.</item>
        <item>There is no floor in this room and you fall to lava.</item>
        <item>Treasure. At last.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="class_dependencies_monsters">
        <item>Whirlwind attack by you sword kills them. You are covered in blood.</item>
        <item>Lighting storm attack makes a day.</item>
        <item>You become invisible.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="class_dependencies_trap">
        <item>You block spikes by enchanted shield.</item>
        <item>You protect yourself with magic sphere.</item>
        <item>You avoid traps by dancing.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="race_dependencies_dog">
        <item>Poor creature, you kill it with mercy.</item>
        <item>You charm the creature with elf natural charisma.</item>
        <item>You\'re dwarf. It laughs at you and chokes to death on its own saliva.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="race_dependencies_succubus">
        <item>Succubus kiss kills you.</item>
        <item>As an elf you resist her kiss. She flee in fear.</item>
        <item>You\'re dwarf. She stares at you a moment and flee in disgust.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="corridors">
        <item>There is corridor on the left.</item>
        <item>There is corridor on the right.</item>
        <item>There is corridor behind you.</item>
        <item>There is corridor towards you</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the left and on the right.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the right and towards you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors towards and behind you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the left and towards you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the left and behind you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the right, towards and behind you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the left, towards and behind you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the right, on the left and towards you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the right, on the left and behind you.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on all sides.</item>
        <item>There are corridors on the right and behind you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drink_results">
        <item>You start with cheap wine. It tastes surprisingly good, and you don\'t feel drunk yet.</item>
        <item>Some kind of sugared cocktail. Pussy drinking, easy contest.</item>
        <item>Stakes are higher now. It is rum. Does they think you are some kind of pirate?</item>
        <item>Time is for whisky. Good one, but you feel a little bit dizzy.</item>
        <item>Here comes a brandy. You are sober enough to enjoy its flavour.</item>
        <item>Vodka makes you regret starting the contest. Your opponent is laughing, the crowd is making dirty jokes.</item>
        <item>Another vodka. Year, the author is a pussy not experienced in drinking, or this tavern has very limited stock.</item>
        <item>Beer. At the beginning you welcome it as a relief, oasis in a desert full of intoxicants.
            But when room begins to float you remember what people say about mixing strong and soft drinks.</item>
        <item>You drink something, the tastes eludes you. Reality eludes you.</item>
        <item>The final drink, is it some kind of contest?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="floor_description">
        <item>First floor is very welcoming. You enter some kind of reception room with comfortable sofas and tables full of sneaks.
        Very tall butler is welcoming you: \"Sir, how may I be of service?\".</item>
        <item>The purpose of the second floor is obvious. It is relaxation zone for the magister and his friends.
        You can see a swimming pool with naked illusionary ladies and sparring zone full of exotic weapons and automatons.</item>
        <item>The Third floor is full of locked rooms, the one with the golden door is especially tempting. You can hear screams from the room
            that is not locked.</item>
        <item>There is library on the left and alchemical laboratory on the right.</item>
        <item>Finally, you enter the bedroom, you see the magister proposing marriage to princess. He is old and ghoulish.
        She is young and beautiful. The princess is hesitating.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices_first_floor">
        <item>You\'re very hungry. Eat sneaks.</item>
        <item>Kill the butler</item>
        <item>Go to the next floor</item>
        <item>Persuade the butler that you\'re the magister\'s business partner</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="results_first_floor">
        <item>The food is poisoned. Bloody magister! You are dying.</item>
        <item>You cut off his head with sword. Blood is all over you.</item>
        <item>You smash his head with staff.</item>
        <item>You impale him with your dagger. Blood is all over you.</item>
        <item>He is already dead. Stop this madness!</item>
        <item>The butler says: \"You cannot go any further"\</item>
        <item>\"It is your life, go on if you want to lose it\"</item>
        <item>You are too drunk to say something clever.</item>
        <item>You\'re in blood, nobody will believe a word.</item>
        <item>You convince him with money from your treasure.</item>
        <item>You were not able to convince him. But it seems he is afraid to actually stop you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices_second_floor">
        <item>Go swimming</item>
        <item>Go to the sparring zone</item>
        <item>Go to the next floor</item>
        <item>Take the greatsword</item>
        <item>Take the smoking bomb</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="results_second_floor">
        <item>You swim with naked ladies. Then you wash your clothes and relax in sofas waiting for it to dry.</item>
        <item>You spar with automatons and see the enchanted Greatsword of Legends.</item>
        <item>You spar with automatons but they are magic immune. They beat you to death.</item>
        <item>You spar with automatons and see the useful smoking bomb.</item>
        <item>That is the best sword you\'ve ever seen. Your power level is increased.</item>
        <item>You love bombs. Your power level is increased.</item>
        <item>You spar a little more</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices_third_floor">
        <item>Try to open golden door</item>
        <item>Check who is screaming</item>
        <item>Go to the next floor</item>
        <item>Use lockpicks</item>
        <item>Smash it</item>
        <item>Take the amulet</item>
        <item>The golden room is empty</item>
        <item>Use whirlwind attack</item>
        <item>Use fireball</item>
        <item>Lock the door</item>
        <item>The room is empty</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="results_third_floor">
        <item>The door is closed you can try to open it with lockpicks or smash it.</item>
        <item>You\'re not drunk enough to smash it.</item>
        <item>There is a spell that can open locks, it exists in another fantasy universe.</item>
        <item>The door is open. There is Amulet of Unimaginable Power.</item>
        <item>You take the amulet, it increases your power level and sadly make you sober.</item>
        <item>The screaming mutant rats attack you.</item>
        <item>Your power level is not enough to kill all of them with one whirlwind attack. One of the rats
        eat your brain. You die!</item>
        <item>You manage to kill all rats with one whirlwind attack. You are lucky today.</item>
        <item>\"Fireball is the most useful spell you will ever learn.\" - said one of your professors. It always saves your skin.</item>
        <item>Your quickly manage to lock the door with lockpicks. You never thought that skill of closing doors may be so useful.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices_fourth_floor">
        <item>Visit library</item>
        <item>Go to the laboratory</item>
        <item>Go to the next floor</item>
        <item>Go deeper into the library</item>
        <item>Drink yellow potion</item>
        <item>Drink blue potion</item>
        <item>Return to the main hall</item>
        <item>Block attack with a shield</item>
        <item>Use whirlwind attack</item>
        <item>Become a berserk</item>
        <item>Use magic shield</item>
        <item>Use shock wave</item>
        <item>Use brain parasites</item>
        <item>Become invisible</item>
        <item>Kill them one by one from shadows</item>
        <item>Distract them with rock.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="results_fourth_floor">
        <item>You are warrior, you smash things not read or teach them. But sometimes it is hard to admit that you\'ve never even learned to read.</item>
        <item>Waste of time!</item>
        <item>From books you learn that the magister likes kittens, there\'re hundreds of books dedicated to kittens.</item>
        <item>Your intuition and wizard class choice allows you to look deeper into the library. You find the Scroll of Kittenball.
        You\'re truly afraid of what it can do. The power level is increased.</item>
        <item>You read another book about kittens, it deepens your knowledge of the universal laws.</item>
        <item>The smell of sulfur, the air is green, you see two bottles - yellow and blue. There is a painting of the yellow kitten on the wall.</item>
        <item>You\'re utterly drunk. You talk a little with the yellow kitten and return to the main hall.</item>
        <item>Your power level is increased.</item>
        <item>You watch the painting of the yellow kitten.</item>
        <item>Shadows surround you, its ninjas, protect yourself.</item>
        <item>I said, \"Protect yourself\". You didn\'t listen and now your head is falling down the stairs.</item>
        <item>You survived the attack, strike back!</item>
        <item>Boring warrior, why always whirlwind attack? Next time be original. Ninjas run in fear.</item>
        <item>It is a massacre. Blood is all over you. You rip out the heart of fallen enemy and eat it.</item>
        <item>Ninjas run in shock.</item>
        <item>You conjure parasites in ninjas brains. They are braindead now.</item>
        <item>Ninjas split up to find you. They search for you everywhere using some stupid pattern.
            The AI in this game is truly bad or you\'re just better ninja.</item>
        <item>You throw the rock to the library. Surprisingly, they follow it, you lock the room behind them.</item>
        <item>You locked the door to the library. Ninjas are quiet, guess they like kittens too.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices_fifth_floor">
        <item>Be persuasive</item>
        <item>Just kill him</item>
        <item>Propose a duel</item>
        <item>Leave in depression</item>
        <item>Go crying</item>
        <item>Run in embarrassment</item>
        <item>Propose marriage</item>
        <item>Propose sex without obligation</item>
        <item>Stay single, stay virgin</item>
        <item>Sometimes it happens</item>
        <item>Use the artifact</item>
        <item>Wait for the attack and block</item>
        <item>Strike</item>
        <item>Proudly walk home</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="results_fifth_floor">
        <item>They are both laughing at you. Of course, all they see is a shrimp with funny beard. All your dreams are crushed in an instance.
            The princess is in another castle. </item>
        <item>Princess screams looking at you. You wander why. The magister is saying: \"I\'ll protect you from
        this monster, my love!\" You realize that your clothes are soaked in blood, you look truly devilish. The magister uses magic shield.</item>
        <item>You\'re too drunk to say something logical.</item>
        <item>You say that love is a burden and it is better to stay lonely till the end of your days. The magister doesn\'t believe you.</item>
        <item>He is bored by your countless attempts and impressed by your determination and stupidity. \"She is all yours\", he says.</item>
        <item>You tell the magister that he is a coward. Instead of conquering his fear and getting a real kitten he find some
        cheap surrogate called woman. The magister is crying. \"She is all yours\", he says.</item>
        <item>The magister uses magic shield. But your power is truly unimaginable. You strike with magic sword and protection sphere surrounding the magister is blown to light particles.
            The magister is dead. Blood is everywhere. The princess screams in terror, then jumps out the window.</item>
        <item>You throw smoking bomb. You throw it with such power that the magister\'s head pops.
            Brains are all over the princess evening dress. She screams in terror, then jumps out the window.</item>
        <item>You use kittenball. The living mass of interconnected kitten upper bodies appears in front of you
        and start moving toward the magister. You glimpse happiness at his face. \"What a glorious death!\" - he shouts. The ball of kittens eats your archenemy alive,
            devour the princess. And then you hear lovely purr, you are lucky that the creature is well-fed.</item>
        <item>Your surprise attack failed. The magister uses magic shield. \"Let it be the duel\", - tha magister says. \"How very noble!\" - the princess laughs.</item>
        <item>\"How very noble!\" - the princess laughs. The magister uses magic shield.</item>
        <item>You don\'t have any artifact.</item>
        <item>The Greatsword of Legends cuts the magic sphere like butter. The magister is dead. The princess seems ecstatic.</item>
        <item>You use the smoke bomb to become invisible. The time passes and the magister starts to think that you
        retreated. He drops the shield. And then you strike. The magister is dead. The princess seems ecstatic.</item>
        <item>You block the lighting ball with magic shield of your own. The magister shield is dropped.</item>
        <item>As a warrior you cannot block magical attacks. But your constitution allows you to survive first lighting strike. The magister shield is dropped.</item>
        <item>You evade the lighting strike. The magister shield is dropped.</item>
        <item>You are not experience enough too use the artifact properly. Magic shield blocks your attack with the Sword of Legends.
        The burning hands attack of your enemy outright kills you.</item>
        <item>You are not experience enough too use the artifact properly. You throw the smoking bomb, it ricochets back smashing your head. You are dead.</item>
        <item>Due to your hesitation the magister has enough time to cast mightier spell. Brain parasites make you braindead.</item>
        <item>You impale the magister heart with the Sword of Legends. The princess seems ecstatic.</item>
        <item>You throw smoking bomb right into the magister mouth. He suffocates from smoke. The princess seems ecstatic.</item>
        <item>Your sword ricochet from the magic sphere surrounding the magister and cut your head off. You die.</item>
        <item>You cannot penetrate the shield. You lose the momentum and magister strikes you with ice spikes. You die.</item>
        <item>You bush the magister with a shield, and bush and bush and bush until he is dead. The princess seems ecstatic.</item>
        <item>You levitate the magister out the window. He screams while falling. The princess seems ecstatic.</item>
        <item>You throw several daggers right into the magister forehead. He is dead, the princess seems ecstatic.</item>
        <item>\"Sorry, alcoholics are not in my taste. You should leave now,\" - she says. To hell with it! You don\'t even sure you\'ll remember this day.</item>
        <item>\"You\'re bloody monster!\" - she runs in terror.</item>
        <item>That was one of your best adventures. But to connect your life with woman? Maybe after another castle.</item>
        <item>\"I heard you\'re pretty rich. So my answer is yes, I wil be your wife!\" - princess says.</item>
        <item>\"You don\'t rich enough for me. Sorry, not interested. Walk away, adventuring filth\".</item>
        <item>Princess moans in passion, too excited to refuse. You are champion, and its your hour of triumph.</item>
        <item>\"Sorry, honey. I\'m not this type of woman\".</item>
        <item>She is too tired to continue.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="retirement_results_human">
        <item>You return to the farmhouse near human capital city where you grew up intended to have a peaceful life.</item>
        <item>You\'ve been an adventurer all of your life and never had a decent job. So your pension is minimum.
            You don\'t even have money to buy seeds and sprouts.</item>
        <item>So, you start beating your neighbours cause you will always be a warrior in your soul.
        First you loot seeds from them, but you do not know how to farm. So you continue beating them to ensure they will work for you.
        After three years of farming you create some kind of rogue kingdom based on slavery. The true king of the realm finally notices it and send an army to
        suppress the rebellion. You flee in terror but the king\'s agents are everywhere leaving you the only option - there is an unexplored continent to the east,
            the land of barbarians, monsters and new weapons. The retirement is postponed, adventures continue.</item>
        <item>So, you start charming your neighbours by some fool magic. They idolize you, give free food and women. After three years of such practice
            your cult spreads. It now opposes the official religion of the human realm - octopusism. The octopsarch of the realm finally notices it and send inquisitors to
        wipe the cult. You flee in terror but the octopsarch\'s agents are everywhere leaving you the only option - there is an unexplored continent to the east,
            the land of barbarians, monsters and new spells. The retirement is postponed, adventures continue.</item>
        <item>So, you start stealing from your neighbours cause you will always be a thief.
        First you loot seeds from them, but you do not know how to farm. So you continue stealing - you steal food, gold, homes. They have no options left than to become your apprentices.
        The thieving guild is born. After three years of growth it now terrorizes the human realm. The militia of the realm finally notices it and send guards to
        finish the guild. You flee in terror but the guards are everywhere leaving you the only option - there is an unexplored continent to the east,
            the land of barbarians, monsters and unexplored wealth. The retirement is postponed, adventures continue.</item>
        <item>Your name is </item>
        <item>and you are a drunkard. You spent all of your time at the local tavern surrounded by like-minded people. It is good till it lasts.</item>
        <item>But you soon spend all your money. Too drunk and depressed about life you die quietly in a gully.</item>
        <item>And it lasts and it lasts. Cause you\'re rich, boy! And people in the tavern like you, you are their generous god
            who buy free beer every morning and every evening. Unfortunately, one day your heart just stops too drunk to go on.</item>
        <item>Unfortunately, there is nothing more dangerous than a drunk wizard. One day the tavern explodes and demon army pours from its ashes.
        The demon lord make you eternally sober as a reward for opening the portal to his domain. What a course! To become drunk again you need to kill the bastard.
        The new adventure awaits.</item>
        <item>And you are truly rich! Your farm prospers because of paid labour. And you don\'t need to work another day. Good food, steady flow of wine,
        beautiful maidens. Your armor and weapons soon become covered with dust, and you don\'t recognize yourself in the mirror anymore.
        People around you talk about an unexplored continent to the east. But you decide to leave adventuring to the young and bold,
            you are too fat anyway. Sometimes it makes you sad.</item>
        <item>And you are truly rich! You develop the method of growing books from garden-beds. All you need is to plant the old book to soil.
        And a dozen new books grow from it, usually a content of a new book copies the content of the old. But sometimes a miracle happens, and something
        new is born. Proud of yourself, you abandon your robe and staff, and you don\'t recognize yourself in the mirror anymore.
        People around you talk about an unexplored continent to the east. But you decide to leave adventuring to the young and bold,
            you are too fat anyway. Sometimes it makes you sad.</item>
        <item>And you are truly rich! You turn your farm into the rehabilitation facility for criminals where they earn their place in society through hard labour.
        You continue to steal from time to time but less and less. Proud of yourself, you abandon your daggers, and you don\'t recognize yourself in the mirror anymore.
        People around you talk about an unexplored continent to the east. But you decide to leave adventuring to the young and bold,
            you are too fat anyway. Sometimes it makes you sad.</item>
        <item>It is supposed to be the best ending, you are rich and the princess is by your side. Delusional fool.
        The princess is very capricious, you buy her expensive jewelery and clothes. But it is never enough, she hates your farm -
        you move to the city, she hates one house - you buy another. But you love her cause she is a hard earn trophy.
        Unfortunately, after five years you run out of money. She soon runs from you to some distant castle. You are broken at first.
        But people around you talk about an unexplored continent to the east. You decide to become an adventurer once more. The new land awaits!</item>
        <item>Sometimes you remember the princess horrible death. It haunts you till the end of your days.</item>
        <item>One more thing, there is lonely kittenball in this world searching for you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="retirement_results_elf">
        <item>You return to the elven woods where you grew up intended to have a peaceful life.</item>
        <item>You\'ve been an adventurer all of your life and elven people are very conservative folks. Your neighbours hates you.
            They call you \"half elf\" and refuse to sell food and clothes.</item>
        <item>So, you start beating your neighbours cause you will always be a warrior in your soul.
        You loot food from them and clothes. But they hate you even more. So you continue beating them to ensure their respect.
        After three years of such a behaviour everyone in the woods wants you dead. Through sacrifice of all dears in the wood they conduct bloody
            ritual conjuring mighty treewalkers and wyverns. You flee in terror but the wyverns are very persistent creatures,
            it leaves you the only option - there is an unexplored continent to the east, the land of barbarians, monsters and new weapons.
            The retirement is postponed, adventures continue.</item>
        <item>So, you start charming your neighbours by some fool magic. They idolize you, give free food and women. After three years of such practice
        your cult spreads transcending the woods. It now opposes the official religion of the human realm - octopusism.
        The octopsarch of the realm finally notices it and send the crusade to burn the woods. It is the genocide, an entire race wiped out.
        You flee in terror but the octopsarch\'s agents are everywhere leaving you the only option - there is an unexplored continent to the east,
        the land of barbarians, monsters and new spells. The retirement is postponed, adventures continue.</item>
        <item>So, you start stealing from your neighbours cause you will always be a thief.
        You loot food and clothes from them, but its never enough for such kleptomaniac as you. So you continue stealing -
        you steal women, gold, home-trees. You become richer and richer, the elven nation becomes poorer and more desperate.
        Some kind of dictator rises to power. Strict curfew is imposed, your fellow colleagues are executed before your eyes.
        You flee in terror but the dictator, your creation, starts the war against the world. There is nowhere to hide which leaves you the only option
        - there is an unexplored continent to the east, the land of barbarians, monsters and unexplored wealth. The retirement is postponed, adventures continue.</item>
        <item>Your name is </item>
        <item>and you are a drunkard. You return to the elven woods where you grew up and spent all of your time draining the juice from the mother tree.
        Her juice is the only alcohol in the woods.</item>
        <item>Soon mother tree dies from the juice loss. You are too drunk to feel any pain when fellow elves execute you.</item>
        <item>No amount of money could have saved you. You are too drunk to feel any pain when fellow elves execute you.</item>
        <item>Unfortunately, there is nothing more dangerous than a drunk wizard. One day the mother tree explodes and demon army pours from its ashes.
        The demon lord make you eternally sober as a reward for opening the portal to his domain. What a course! To become drunk again you need to kill the bastard.
        The new adventure awaits.</item>
        <item>And you are truly rich! Unfortunately the human money is nothing for primitive elven economy. Foreign exchange is not developed here. You move to the
        human realm and start the Warrior Guild. It becomes the place of growth and nourishment for young adventurers. And when rumors about an unexplored continent
        to the east reaches the guild halls you decide to leave the excitement of exploring it to young members of the guild. Sometimes it makes you sad.
        But you are also so proud of your wards.</item>
        <item>And you are truly rich! Unfortunately the human money is nothing for primitive elven economy. Foreign exchange is not developed here. You move to the
        human realm and start the Wizard Guild. It becomes the place of growth, nourishment and knowledge for young adventurers. And when rumors about an unexplored continent
        to the east reaches the guild halls you decide to leave the excitement of exploring its mysteries to young members of the guild. Sometimes it makes you sad.
        But you are also so proud of your wards.</item>
        <item>And you are truly rich! Unfortunately the human money is nothing for primitive elven economy. Foreign exchange is not developed here. You move to the
        human realm and start the Thieving Guild. It becomes the place of growth, nourishment and enrichment for young adventurers. And when rumors about an unexplored continent
        to the east reaches the guild halls you decide to leave the excitement of stealing its treasures to young members of the guild. Sometimes it makes you sad.
        But you are also so proud of your wards.</item>
        <item>It is supposed to be the best ending, you are rich and the princess is by your side. Delusional fool.
        The human money is nothing for primitive elven economy. Foreign exchange is not developed here.
        What is more, the princess is very capricious, she demands expensive jewelery and clothes and hates the woods.
        You move to the human city, she hates one house - you buy another. But you love her because she is a hard earn trophy.
        Unfortunately, after five years you run out of money. She soon runs from you to some distant castle. You are broken at first.
        But people around you talk about an unexplored continent to the east. You decide to become an adventurer once more. The new land awaits!</item>
        <item>Sometimes you remember the princess horrible death. It haunts you till the end of your days.</item>
        <item>One more thing, there is lonely kittenball in this world searching for you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="retirement_results_dwarf">
        <item>You return to the underground dwarven city where you grew up intended to end your life blowing yourself in an abandoned mine.
        Your experience in the outside world was too cruel for you to bear.</item>
        <item>You\'ve been an adventurer all of your life and never had a decent job. So your pension is minimum.
            You don\'t even have money to buy an explosive.</item>
        <item>So, you start beating yourself with a pick. Good that you forgot to take your helmet off. After a seventh blow to the head you notice a beautiful human lady
        lustfully staring at you.</item>
        <item>So, you start channeling deadly spell to kill yourself. Good that your concentration fails you - you notice a beautiful human lady
        lustfully staring at you.</item>
        <item>So, you put a knife to your throat. Good that you are too coward to do it. After the fifth attempt you notice a beautiful human lady
            lustfully staring to you.</item>
        <item>You fall in love, she appears to be immortal shape-shifter woman with a fetish for dwarves. She likes brewing ale, can take any form you want,
        she even grows beard from time to time like any decent dwarven woman. You ask her to marry you, she agrees. She was an adventurer too and
            has enough money so that both of you could not work a single day. But you decide to start a tavern. Soon you will be a happy father. Yes,
        this is the best \"happily ever after\" ending in this game.</item>
        <item>Your name is </item>
        <item>and you are a drunkard too drunk to kill yourself. You spent all of your time at the local tavern surrounded by like-minded people. It is good till it lasts.</item>
        <item>But you soon spend all your money. Too drunk and depressed about life you die quietly in a gully.</item>
        <item>And it lasts and it lasts. Cause you\'re rich, boy! And people in the tavern like you, you are their generous god
            who buy free beer every morning and every evening. One day you see a beautiful human lady lustfully staring at you. You fall in love.
            And love makes you sober. She appears to be immortal shape-shifter woman with a fetish for dwarves. She likes brewing ale, can take any form you want.
            You ask her to marry you, she agrees. She was an adventurer too and has enough money so that both of you could not work a single day.
            Unfortunately, after five years of happiness your heart stops beating weakened by the years of drunkenness.</item>
        <item>And you are truly rich to buy an explosive. So you go to the distant abandoned mine to kill yourself. There you meet a dwarven lady with a long white beard.
        It seems she has come here with the same gaul. You fall in love and marry her. At your wedding you explode the mine that could become the grave for
            both of you. You decide that your children will never visit the surface.</item>
        <item>Sometimes you remember the princess horrible death. It haunts you till the end of your days.</item>
        <item>One more thing, there is lonely kittenball in this world searching for you.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>